import { FAQ } from "@/types/faq";

export const infoData: FAQ[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is BEYMUN?",
    answer: "BEYMUN, a student-led conference organized by AUB students, seeks to enrich individuals about global politics, diplomacy, and conflict resolution while embodying the goal of simulating the United Nations, fostering debate and problem-solving skills among participants representing various countries to address global issues in a collaborative and educational setting."
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "When and where will BEYMUN take place?",
    answer: "This year's conference will take place at the AUB campus. The exact dates will be announced soon.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who can participate in BEYMUN?",
    answer: "Any high school or university students who have an interest in debating, resolving problems, and discussing global issues are welcome to participate in BEYMUN.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "How do I register for BEYMUN?",
    answer: "To register for the 2024 conference, you can complete the online registration form by accessing the link",
    link: 'https://forms.gle/6ey6vjWWZUfADoySA',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What committees will be available at BEYMUN?",
    answer: "The committees at BEYMUN cover diverse aspects, including technology, economic, social, humanitarian, and innovative topics. For specific details and committee names, access the link",
    link: '/committees-hs',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the theme for this year’s BEYMUN conference?",
    answer: "The theme for this year is 'Rise Like a Phoenix', reflecting the fundamental principles of strength, resilience, and peace, underscoring our collective capacity to overcome obstacles and display perseverance amid periods of uncertainty.",
  }, 
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "How much does it cost to participate in BEYMUN? ",
    answer: "Cost information are found",
    link: '/pricing'
  }, 
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Are there any scholarships or financial aid available for participants?",
    answer: "If you require financial assistance to participate in BEYMUN, you can apply for a scholarship through the same registration link indicating that you need a scholarship",
    link: '/register'
  }, 
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Can I participate in BEYMUN if I have no prior Model United Nations experience?",
    answer: "No prior Model United Nations (MUN) experience is required for BEYMUN as training sessions will be provided, introducing delegates to conference skills, with materials sent in advance for reference.",
  }, 
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Is there a dress code for BEYMUN?",
    answer: "A formal dress code is mandatory for BEYMUN, and non-compliance may jeopardize delegates’ final grades at the conference.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Will food be provided at BEYMUN?",
    answer: "Intermissions, refreshments and water will be available during the event.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Can I apply to be a delegate for a specific country or committee?",
    answer: "Country distribution, determined by delegation size, will be organized by conference planners, ensuring equitable assignments. However, delegates have the autonomy to specify their preferences in the registration application.",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Are there any social events planned during BEYMUN?",
    answer: "A social evening will be organized featuring icebreaker activities, alongside numerous chances for delegates to network with guest speakers.",
  }, 
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Is there a minimum or maximum age requirement to participate in BEYMUN?",
    answer: "BEYMUN is a conference catering to both high school and university students.",
  }, 
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Can I receive a certificate of participation for attending BEYMUN?",
    answer: "A certificate of participation will be granted to delegates attending all committee sessions, with no excused absences, ensuring equal opportunities for all committed participants.",
  }, 
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "How can I stay updated on BEYMUN news and announcements?",
    answer: "Make sure to follow our Instagram, X and TikTok accounts, and to regularly check our website for posted updates.",
    link: '/social-links'
  }, 
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "Who can I contact if I have further questions or need assistance regarding BEYMUN?",
    answer: "Feel free to reach out to our registration team at beymun@aub.edu.lb for assistance with the registration process or any other inquiries.",
  }, 
];